Adam Morris

Full-Time Student

Email: amorris2003@gmail.com Mobile: +61 422 464 465 GitHub: @aimorris

About Me

Full-time year 12 student, seeking casual or part-time work for a steady income. I am also currently volunteering at the RSPCA and running a private piano tutoring business. I have 4+ years experience developing front-end applications in JavaScript, HTML, and CSS and have contributed to large codebases such as Mozilla, Exercism, Lichess, and others.

Work Experience

RSPCA: Volunteer Animal Care Assistant

January 2020 - Present

Cleaning enclosures, walking and feeding dogs, providing enrichment to puppies and dogs for adoption.

Exercism Maintainer

January 2020 - Present

Maintaining the JavaScript, CoffeeScript, PureScript, and Haskell language tracks in the Exercism v3 codebase.

Private Piano Tutor

July 2019 - January 2020

Contributing front-end solutions to issues in the lichess.org site.

Lichess Developer

August 2019 - Present

Maintaining the JavaScript, CoffeeScript, PureScript, and Haskell language tracks in the Exercism v3 codebase.

Domino's Pizza: In-store Team Member

February 2017 - July 2018

Preparing food, welcoming and serving customers, cleaning workspaces, and training new employees.

Education

Responsible Service of Alcohol

SITHFAB002 through Clear To Work

AMEB Practice of Music (Piano)

Certified up to grade 6.

AMEB Practice of Music (Clarinet)

Certified up to grade 2.

AMEB Theory of Music

Certified up to grade 5.

Kelvin Grove State College

Chemistry, Biology, Physics, Specialist Mathematics, Mathematics Methods, and English.

Awards

UNSW Principal's Award

2016

High distinction in the UNSW ICAS in Digital Technologies

Distinction in the UNSW ICAS in Mathematics $_{\mbox{\scriptsize 2016}}$

Distinction in the Australian History competition 2016

Merit in the Queensland Interschool Teams Chess Championships 2016